{
    "id": "07f7f8be7b6d410da8b9be47ba1b1863",
    "title": "Modal Verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "682d383e926243b4b60eb9dfaaecdba2",
            "title": "Modal Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You'll like John. He ______ be a little annoying, I believe, but I think you'll get on well with him.",
                    "answers": [
                        "could",
                        "must",
                        "shall",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If no one interrupts her, she ______ go on talking all night.",
                    "answers": [
                        "shall",
                        "will",
                        "should",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ______ return the magazine to me now. You may keep it until next Friday.",
                    "answers": [
                        "can't",
                        "mustn't",
                        "needn't",
                        "may not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "-- Must I renew the book now?-- No, you __________, but you __________ that yesterday.",
                    "answers": [
                        "mustn't ------ should do",
                        "needn't ------ should have done",
                        "may not ------ should do",
                        "can't ------ should have done"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Difficult as the task was, we ______ finish it ahead of time and therefore we were highly praised for it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "could",
                        "had to",
                        "were able to",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ______ chat for hours on end if you give her a chance.",
                    "answers": [
                        "shall",
                        "should",
                        "must",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "I parked my car here, but now it's gone. Where ______ it be?",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "could",
                        "may",
                        "ought"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Each time my uncle came from New York, he ______ bring me a lot of books.",
                    "answers": [
                        "should",
                        "would",
                        "might",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He's just joking. I don't think you __________ it seriously.",
                    "answers": [
                        "need to take",
                        "need taking",
                        "need take",
                        "need in taking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The fire spread through the hotel very quickly, but everyone ______ get out.",
                    "answers": [
                        "had to",
                        "could",
                        "would",
                        "was able to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}